parkopedia.co.uk 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

  * About Us
  * FAQ
  * Testimonials
  * Contact Us
  * Twitter

This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") is inferred into the Terms and Conditions of the Website. Therefore the User must read and agree to this Policy prior to using the services provided by the Website. This Policy applies to all of the services offered by the Website. If you have any queries regarding this Policy please contact us prior to using any of the services.

In this Policy the words and phrases shall have the meaning given in the Terms and Conditions save as when indicated below:

1\. User Information 

To enable the Website to perform the full range of services the Website may collect the following types of information:

**1.1** \- User Information. When the User registers with the Website the User submits Registration Details;

**1.2** \- Cookies. When the User visits the Website the Website sends one or more cookies to the computer being used to access the Website. Cookies are used to enhance the User’s experience and interection with the Website by storing User preferences and tracking User trends. For your information it is possible to disable cookies by adjusting your browser, however it will reduce the services available to you. 

**1.3** \- When the User accesses the Website, the Website servers record information that your browser automatically sends whenever the User visits any website. These may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**1.4** \- Communications. When any communication, of any form, electronic or non electronic, is sent to the Website, the website may retain these communication in order to keep an accurate history of all correspondence which will help the Website provide the User with a complete and through service.

**1.5** \- Associated Sites. The Website may from time to time use its services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that is provide to those sites may be sent to the Website in order to deliver the best service possible. Any information gathered in this way is processed in accordance with this Policy. 

2\. The User's Choice

When a User registers for the service he provides his Registration Details (as defined in the Terms and Conditions) if the Website intends to use the Registration Details in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then the Website will seek the Users prior permission. Such permission maybe declined, in which case the Website may not be able to provide those services to you.

3\. Personal Information

The Website will only share personal information with a third party in the following instances:

**3.1** \- the Website has the Users permission. The Website requires that the User opt-in for the sharing of any sensitive personal information as stated in this Policy at clause 2.

**3.2** \- The Website have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to

**3.2.1** \- satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, enforce applicable Terms and Conditions, including investigation of potential violations thereof,

**3.2.2** \- detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or

**3.2.3** \- protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Website including Users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**3.3** \- If the Website becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, the Website will provide notice if personal information is to be transferred and subject to a privacy policy different to this Policy.

**3.4** \- The Website may share with third parties certain pieces of information which does not serve to identify individuals for example; number of Users who searched for a particular area, or how many Users clicked on a advertisement or sponsored link.

4\. Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please contact us.

5\. Payments

We do not store credit card details.

6\. Changes to the Policy

The Website may amend the Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to the Policy, Users will be notified by a prominent message on the website.
